LIAM FISHER

As a Philosophy, Music, and Computer Science graduate, Liam has a diverse set of strengths. He has worked on teams to program a daycare registration app, implement a Fibonacci heap data structure, manage the full life cycle of data from cleaning to entry to visualization, as well as held people-oriented roles such as teaching and promoting sustainable energy initiatives.



CONTACT

- fisherl.lkf@gmail
- +1(630)946-8263
- 60126 Elmhurst. IL
- liamfish77.github.io/
- @liamfish77
- Liam Fisher

SKILLS

Programming

Python C++ Bash Java

SQL LaTeX

Operating Systems

Linux **MacOS** Windows

Software & Tools

Visualisation (Tableau Public)

Data handling/analysis **Google Workspace**

Relevant college courses

Calculus sequence **Graph theory Data structures** Algorithm analysis **Combinatorics**

Languages

Japanese

English Spanish (Advanced Spanish Immersion in Spain)

CERTIFICATES

Tableau Certified Associate Salesforce Security Superbadge HP Summer Scholar

PROFESSIONAL OVERVIEW

Having worked as the head of recruitment for the Sunrise Movement, a canvasser for the Wisconsin Public Interest Research Group, an intern for Chicago's Forest Preserve Foundation, and a K-8 teacher during the pandemic; Liam's experience has a through-line of advocating for the common good using his skills with technology and communication.

* WORK HISTORY

7/2021-Present

♀ Old St. Mary's Catholic School, Chicago, IL

K - 8 Music & Comp Sci Teacher

Developing and teaching the Old St. Mary's music curriculum Teaching computer science and STEM classes to 3rd - 8th grade

1/2021-Present

STEM Hands On. Chicago, IL

Instructor

Building robotics, drones, circuit boards and additional items needed for lessons Teaching lesson plans focused on STEM skills

1/2020-12/2020

Lawrence University, Appleton, WI

Audiovisual Technician

Set up sound, lights and projectors for LU events, rehearsals, and performances Moved furniture and instruments to accommodate specifications made by event holders

EDUCATION

1 09/2016 - 12/2020

♀ Lawrence University Appleton, WI

Bachelor of Arts: Philosophy

Minors: Music & Computer Science

ACHIEVEMENTS, HONOURS AND AWARDS

- Cum Laude, Dean's List each semester, GPA 3.8/4
- 2020 Downbeat Award Recipient
- ₱ Head of Rhythm Section for Lawrence University Jazz Ensemble

WORK DAY WHEEL CHART

